[{"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "So you're not exactly on the -- on the breadline, are you?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yes, in many ways.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "But do you feel you have?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it -- it depends.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "When you look back on it, how tough was it, in reality, do you think?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, I had to make the choice personally.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "How did you manage, do you think, to make that break, to get out of that culture?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "When that prison door shut for the first time and you were in the cell -- can you remember how you felt?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "It did, but it's also very hard because now you're back into that environment and it's not like all of a sudden I could say -- well, I grew up in this bad place and I don't want to be around these guys anymore, so I'm going to move to California or I'm going to move to New York.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Did your behavioral pattern change dramatically when you came out?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Well, that real life experience is so much more powerful, I think, in my job, especially as an actor, than anything, and also in my business approach.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Rough though it was, and tough, what were the things that you got from that lifestyle which have been of benefit to you in the new world that you have?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I'm not.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Are you -- are you a very tough negotiator?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Do the streets ever leave you?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "AHLBERG: A very clear focus on what's important, expressing my gratitude for all the blessings that have been bestowed upon me, and a reminder everyday of what I need to do and what I need to focus on and what I need to stay away from.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "What does it bring you?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "I pray to be a good servant to God, a father, a husband, a son, a friend, brother and uncle, a good neighbor, a good leader to those that look up to me and a good follower to those that are serving God and doing the right thing and people that it can look up to and, you know, try to emulate.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "When you pray, what do you pray for?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "But it's a very -- it is a very raw movie, isn't it?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "You know, I -- I probably -- that would be probably the only reason why I'd ever go back to prison, if I had to do something to protect my family, you know, and there was no other -- there was no other means of doing it.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Do you know the answer?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "It all depends on which part of my family.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "What do you family make of your career path?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Well, my kids could care less and they hate it when, you know, people come up to us when we're in public and, you know, and the paparazzi and stuff like that.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "What are the positive parts and what are the negative?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "But the character was sort of probably had to have one and you did a deal not to have one, but the deal was you would still appear naked on screen, is that right?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Tell me about the deal.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "How did you hear about that?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "But a deal worked in to keep your wife happy?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Daniel Day-Lewis, Russell Crowe, Denzel Washington --", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "I mean, who -- who do you really rate out there in the acting world?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "-- kind of actors.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "-- and a great actor?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Very.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Are you sad \"Entourage\" is over?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "That's why you need people around you that will keep you grounded.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "What do you think of the basic shallowness of Hollywood, the fact that if you're a hot star, everyone is crawling all over you, kissing ass, the moment it goes cold, boom?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "I want to play you.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Have you got one out there that you think, if I get the chance, that's what I want to do?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "That kind of lofty ambition?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Well, it's -- it's extremely difficult.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "If you're President Obama and you're trying to deal with this obviously huge problem, what do you do about that problem, that part of it, the need to finance a family?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "And I say the odds of you doing that are slim to none.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "You dropped out, then you went to prison and now you're this billion dollar movie star?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "She's the most important person in my life.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "How important has your wife been to you?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "A lot of different things.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "What's in the pipeline?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I would probably choose not quitting school because that's when everything started to go downhill.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "When you look back over this amazing career you've had, with all the twists and turns, if I had the power to let you relive one moment again, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Blessed.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "You know what, he was around long enough to see me turn it around.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What do you think your dad would have made of the Mark Wahlberg sitting in front of me now?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "One of the things that he said when he first arrived in Prague, he said, remember, I'm not making a civil rights movie right here.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "In a different way, but a similar kind of struggle?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "No, it's par -- it's par for the course.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Is it shocking?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Are you surprised that we're three years after President Barack Obama is elected, and you're still having to have this kind of battle in a place like Hollywood?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "I hope -- you know, I'm an optimist, so I think less racist.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Do you believe that since Barack Obama was elected, America has become more or less racist?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "You know, it's a hard job.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "How do you think Barack Obama's been doing as president?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "It's almost an impossible job.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "But, my God, how do you deal with all of the pressures coming from every possible place?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "ORGAN: Doesn't the movie that you've made here -- doesn't that absolutely -- and, indeed, the making of this movie, doesn't that show you that you have to have courage?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "Well said what you just said.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "You have to have an instinct for taking a big gamble and for pushing against that kind of partisan view, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "It's unbelievable.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "How big is this Tebow thing?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "I'm not the biggest NFL fan because I'm not American.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Do you like it?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "You feel an energy, yes.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "When you do the Tebow, you feel this surging power, don't you?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "It came from a writer, Patrick Reilly (ph).", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Tell me about Bowie and you?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "I do know him.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Do you know Bowie?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "We would just -- for only like a week or something.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "You were e-mail buddies with David Bowie?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "Yeah, then we both put on the same show that each other were watching.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "And you're email each other saying, what are you watching on TV?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "I think I lost it now.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Do you have his e-mail address?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "I think he's 65 years old, David Bowie.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "How cool is David Bowie?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "Yes, he can finally get a free bus pass in Britain.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "If I can't email Bowie, can I e-mail you?", "qSentId": 758}, {"answer": "You can go through my publicist.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "I can't e-mail you?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "He's going to kill it.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "Is he going to kill him?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "I can't even do it, because I don't want to take his impression.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "Can you do it?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "I would do his impression.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "But if you were doing me, what would you do?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "It's just great.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "What are my weaknesses?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "You have to.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 793, "question": "Why would I love that?", "qSentId": 792}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120113pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "You are, aren't you?", "qSentId": 818}]